<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" ?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Our Trips</title><description></description><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html</link><atom:link
    href="https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/feed.rss"
    rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"
/><language>en</language><generator>Ignite v0.5.0</generator><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2024_Victoria_And_South_Australia</guid><title>Victoria and South Australia</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2024_Victoria_And_South_Australia</link><description><![CDATA[Just a quick trip to Adelaide and Kinglake to visit family. On the way we stopped at the Barossa Valley and visited the wonderful Dali exhibition at the D’Arenberg Winery in McLaren Vale. We also spent a few days at Halls Gap in the Grampians, visiting the beautiful waterfalls and lookouts in the area.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 06 Nov 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2023_Florida,_Georgia_And_South_Carolina</guid><title>Florida, Georgia and South Carolina</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2023_Florida,_Georgia_And_South_Carolina</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 17 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2019_Italy</guid><title>Northern Italy</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2019_Italy</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 21 Aug 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2018_Mount_Rushmore_And_Yellowstone_NP</guid><title>Mount Rushmore and Yellowstone NP</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2018_Mount_Rushmore_And_Yellowstone_NP</link><description><![CDATA[An interesting trip marred by us both having bad colds, or worse. Still managed to see what we came for. Highlights were a helicopter ride over Mount Rushmore and surrounds, the Needles highway, a visit to the Badlands National Park and the Mammoth Site at Hot Springs.  After a long drive to beautiful Red Lodge, visiting Devils Tower on the way, we took a breathtaking drive over the Beartooth Highway, the highest highway in North America, to Yellowstone National Park. This was our second visit to the park and it didn’t disappoint, with some of the geysers being extra active and a bear appearing near the side of the road.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 15 Aug 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2017_Greece</guid><title>Greece</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2017_Greece</link><description><![CDATA[This was a wonderful trip with so much history to take in. We stuck to the mainland this time, first visiting Athens then staying for a week each at 2 different locations in the Peloponnese, visiting the ancient sites in the area. This was followed by a road trip to visit the fantastic Vikos Gorge, Ioannina, Meteora and Royal Tombs of Philip II and family at Vergina. Then a relaxing week in a mountainous village near Volos. The village had the most dangerous road to get to it you’ll ever see, including driving 200 meters along a light rail track with cliff on one side, through a rail tunnel, with a bend in it, to the village! Fortunately the train only came a few times a day and went fairly slowly but after doing it a few times we decided to park the car at the bottom of the mountain and walk up and down. After that, another road trip to Delphi and surrounds. Only downside was we had 900 photos to sort through when we got back.]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 16 May 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2016_New_Zealand</guid><title>New Zealand</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2016_New_Zealand</link><description><![CDATA[On the spur of the moment we decided to take advantage of a - short lived - direct flight from Canberra to Wellington. Our main goal was to visit the beautiful Art Deco town of Napier and the surrounding wineries of Hawke’s Bay. After that we drove around the northern coast on to Rotorua and then down to Mount Egmont for a wonderful few days visiting several spectacular gardens in the area.]]></description><pubDate>Sat, 12 Nov 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2016_Scotland</guid><title>Scotland</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2016_Scotland</link><description><![CDATA[We had hoped to visit Scotland as part of our trip through the UK nearly 30 years ago but we completely ran out of time on that trip, so it was great to finally get here. As with Ireland we were really lucky with the weather, with sunshine and blue skies almost every day. After a great week in Edinburgh we left for the countryside, visiting lots of castles, old stately homes, ancient burial sites, battlegrounds and churches as well as some beautiful gardens. The scenery, especially in the Western Highlands and Skye, was fantastic. Stayed mostly in B&B’s along the way. In places they got pretty scarce and we had a few close calls, with sleeping in the car becoming an option. Thankfully that never happened.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 16 May 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2015_Margaret_River</guid><title>WA - Fremantle and Margaret River</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2015_Margaret_River</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 31 Aug 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2015_New_York_And_New_England</guid><title>New York and New England</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2015_New_York_And_New_England</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Sun, 24 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2014_Italy</guid><title>Central Italy</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2014_Italy</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 05 May 2014 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2013_Phuket</guid><title>Phuket and Malacca</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2013_Phuket</link><description><![CDATA[We’d enjoyed our previous stay at Phuket so much that we decided to do the same thing the next year. We had a different villa in the complex this time but it was still excellent with a private pool and all. We spent much of the month relaxing and going ‘local’. It did rain quite a bit more this time but we still managed to spend a lot of time out and about and eating at lots of excellent restaurants. At the end of our trip we spent a few days in the old Malaysian trading port of Malacca which we had last visited 30 years before.]]></description><pubDate>Sun, 21 Jul 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2013_New_Mexico_And_Arizona</guid><title>New Mexico and Arizona</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2013_New_Mexico_And_Arizona</link><description><![CDATA[This trip had been on our bucket list for quite a while and it didn’t disappoint. The variety of places we visited made every day fascinating. Everything from Titan missile silos to petrified forests, huge meteor craters, gigantic caves at Carlsbad, the ancient Indian settlements at Mesa Verde and the beautiful Canyon de Chelly and Grand Canyon, as well as the interesting old towns of Albuquerque and Santa Fe. Los Alamos and the whole Trinity thing was also very interesting as was the National Solar Observatory, the Very Large Array, and Lowell observatory at Flagstaff, where they discovered Pluto.]]></description><pubDate>Mon, 20 May 2013 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2012_Phuket</guid><title>Sri Lanka and Phuket</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2012_Phuket</link><description><![CDATA[We started off in Sri Lanka by visiting many of the ancient temple complexes in the northern part of the island that we had missed the last time we were there. That trip was cut short by the outbreak of a Civil War and unfortunately this meant that this time much of the infrastructure was still in a shambles. It was still quite interesting but 10 days was enough. This was followed by a wonderfully relaxing 1 month stay at a beautiful villa on Phuket. It was the rainy season so the villa was amazingly good value and we were lucky that it only rained on a few days. We had a car for the whole month so spent quite a few days touring the islands various beaches and checking out some new villas for sale, pretending to be potential buyers.]]></description><pubDate>Sun, 22 Jul 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2012_Ireland</guid><title>Ireland</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2012_Ireland</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Sat, 05 May 2012 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2011_West_Coast_USA</guid><title>West Coast USA</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2011_West_Coast_USA</link><description><![CDATA[All our trips to the US have been really interesting and this one was no exception. Virtually every day there was something different to see, from the majestic redwood forests and coastline of Northern California to Mount St. Helens, Portland and the waterfalls of the Columbia River Gorge, Seattle and the Boeing Factory, the Grand Coulee Dam and of course Yellowstone National Park and the Tetons. There were also some fun surprises like the unusual houses in Eureka and the remnants of the Aircraft Nuclear Propulsion experiment at EBR-1. A really great trip.]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 11 May 2011 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2010_Vietnam</guid><title>Darwin and Vietnam</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2010_Vietnam</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 31 Aug 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2010_Tasmania</guid><title>Tasmania</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2010_Tasmania</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Wed, 28 Apr 2010 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2008_Cambodia</guid><title>Cambodia and Thailand</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2008_Cambodia</link><description><![CDATA[This was just a quick trip mainly to visit Ankor Wat in Cambodia. We spent 3 days following in the footsteps of Lara Croft as we explored the temple ruins during the day, followed by eating and drinking at some of the wonderful restaurants along the main food street of Siem Reap. This was followed by a relaxing two week holiday on the island of Phuket, staying at a luxury resort.]]></description><pubDate>Tue, 01 Jan 2008 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2006_Fiji</guid><title>Fiji</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2006_Fiji</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jul 2006 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item><item><guid isPermaLink="true">https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2005_Hawaii</guid><title>Hawaii</title><link>https://www.zegelin.com/ourtravels/index.html/2005_Hawaii</link><description><![CDATA[]]></description><pubDate>Thu, 22 Sep 2005 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><dc:creator><![CDATA[Peter]]></dc:creator></item></channel></rss>